cryptoassetrating.com 2018-10-13

# PrivacyPolicy

### Privacy Principles

Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by Crypto Asset Rating (“ANS”). This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect when you access our website, mobile applications, tokens and wallets (collectively, our “Online Services”) Since we may gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This Privacy Policy discloses what information we gather and how we use it. The private information you provide on the Online Services will be used only for its intended purpose. **BY VISITING, USING AND ACCESING THE SERVICES, YOU CONSENT TO THE DATA PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS STATEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH OUT PRIVACY PRACTICES, DO NOT USE THE SERVICES.**

### Our Pledge to You

We are committed to maintaining your trust and pledge the following: _Transparency._ We will keep you informed of our privacy practices.   
_Safety._ While we cannot promise perfection, we have implemented security tools that are designed to safeguard your information in accordance with industry standards.   
_You are in the driver’s seat._ We will ask for your permission before we share your personal information with third parties, in accordance with this Privacy Policy. _We tell you when our privacy policies and practices change._ We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we do, we will let you know by appropriate means such as by posting the revised policy on this page with a new “Last Updated” date. All changes will become effective when posted unless indicated otherwise. 

## Information we collect

**Information You Provide to Us.** We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, the types of personal information we may collect from you when you visit or use our Online Services include your name, email address, mailing address, social security number, telephone number(s), account numbers, user name and password. As a general rule, you have the right not to provide the foregoing information when dealing with the Online Services.   
**Information We Collect Automatically When You Use the Online Services.** In addition to the personal information described above, we may collect certain information about your use of our Online Services. 
  * Log Information 
We collect log information about your use of the online services, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the page you visited before navigating to our online services. 
  * Device Information 
We collect information about the computer or mobile device you use to access our online services, including the hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers and mobile network information. 
  * Location Information 
We may collect information about the location of your device each time you access or use one of our mobile applications or otherwise consent to the collection of this information. 
  * Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies 
Our third-party partners or we may use cookies (as well as web beacons or other technologies) to collect and store this and other information about your visit to, or use of, our online services. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us improve our online services and your experience, and to see which areas and features of our online services are popular. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our online services or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits and understand usage and campaign effectiveness. We may later associate the usage and other information we collect online with personal information about you, as permitted or required by law. For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see "Your Choices" below. 
  * Information We Collect From Other Sources 
We may also collect information about you from additional online and offline sources including commercially available third-party sources, such as consumer reporting agencies, for the purposes of verifying eligibility and securely offering our services to you. We may combine this information with the personal and other information we have collected about you under this Privacy Policy. 

## Use of Information

We may use the information we collect from you for various purposes, including to:In addition to the personal information described above, we may collect certain information about your use of our online services. 
  * Help us deliver our Services; 
  * Administer, evaluate and improve our business (including developing new products and services, improving existing products and services, performing data analytics, monitoring and analyzing trends, and performing accounting, auditing and other internal functions); 
  * Communicate information to you at the request of our partners; 
  * Manage our risks; 
  * Market our Services and products; 
  * Comply with and enforce applicable laws and regulations, relevant industry standards, contractual obligations and our policies; and 
  * Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected. 
We may also use data that we collect on an aggregate or de-identified basis for various business purposes, where permissible under applicable laws and regulations. 

## How we use your Information

We use information collected as described in this Privacy Statement for the following: **Operation**
  * Operate, maintain and improve the Online Services; 
  * Provide you with interest-based ads, communications, and offers for products and services from us based on your precise geolocation; 
  * Manage your account, including processing payments and refunds; 
  * Send you reminders, technical notices, updates, security alerts, support and administrative messages and marketing messages; 
  * Answer your questions and respond to your requests; 
  * Ensure that content from our Online Services is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer or device for accessing the Online Services; 
  * Carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including the Terms and Conditions; and 
  * Notify you when there are changes to any products or services we offer or provide though the Online Services. 
**Usage and Analytics**
  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns;
  * Perform analytics and conduct customer research;
  * Evaluate your eligibility for certain types of offers, products or services that may be of interest to you;
  * Analyze advertising effectiveness; and
  * Communicate and provide additional information that may be of interest to you about us and our business partners. 

## How we disclose your Information

We may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy: 
  * With ANS partners as part of the delivery of our Online Services to you;
  * With affiliates, consultants, and other service providers when we believe it will enhance the Online Services and products we can provide to you or for legal and routine business reasons. For example, we may share selected details when checking your identity for indicators of fraud during sign up or when providing alerts. These parties are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
  * As required or permitted by law, such as to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements, comply with a subpoena, bankruptcy proceedings, or similar legal process. For example, we may share information with regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to comply with legal requirements. We may share information with third parties where appropriate to protect against fraud or verify or enforce our terms of use, our other rights, or other applicable policies.
  * In connection with a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets; you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership, uses of your personal information, and choices you may have regarding your personal information.
  * Between and among our current and future parents, affiliates, subsidiaries and other companies under common control and ownership; and
  * With your consent or at your direction.
We may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you. 

## Changing yourData Collection Settings

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. You may need to adjust the settings on your computer and/or device to restrict the collection of information by the Online Services, but this may prevent you from accessing all of the features of the Online Services. 
  * Tracking Technologies: You may be able to set your browser or device to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable or refuse cookies or block the use of other tracking technologies, some parts of the Services may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
  * Location Information: You can choose whether or not to allow the Online Services to collect and use real-time information about your device’s location through the device’s privacy settings. If you block the use of location information, some parts of the Online Services may then be inaccessible or not function properly. For example, you have the ability to only allow manual geolocation (rather than using their device’s auto locating functionality), but the provision of at least one piece of location data (i.e. you search location) may be a requirement for the Online Services to function.

###  Children Under Thirteen 

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13). If you are under the age of thirteen please do not submit any personal data through the Online Services. 

###  Security 

We take our responsibility to protect the privacy and confidentiality of your information, including personal information, very seriously. We take reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. The safety and security of your information also depends on you. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any person using the Services. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet and mobile services is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted through our Online Services. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures we provide. 

If you suspect that there has been a breach of the security of your data you should contact us at [info@cryptoassetrating.com](mailto:info@cryptoassetrating.com) and include details of the nature of the breach, the date of the breach, and the full circumstances of the breach. 

### Your Choices

We provide you with relevant and appropriate choices regarding the sharing of personal information. CAR will provide you with details about whether we hold any of your personal information. If you wish to request access, or deletion of your personal information please contact us at Contact Note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe, usually within five business days. 

### Changes to this Statement

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect company and customer feedback. We encourage you to periodically review this Policy to be informed of how we are protecting your information. 

### Contact us

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us through the Crypto Asset Rating website: Rating
